Cioni, Peter J. Labor Agreement Collection 5916
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Series I. COMPANY PUBLICATIONS & DOCUMENTS
  - Sub-Series A. AGREEMENTS
    - Clark Equipment Company and IAM, Local 701 (Automobile Mechanics), 1956-1976; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 2, Folder 1)
      - Item 2: Clark Equipment Company and IAM, Local 701 (Automobile Mechanics)., 1961-1964; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 2, Folder 1)
        10/25/61 - 10/24/64.
      - Item 3: Clark Equipment Company, Industrial Truck Division, Chicago Sales and Service Branch, 1962-1965; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 2, Folder 1)
        12/4/62 - 12/4/65.
      - Item 4: Clark Equipment Company, Chicago-Calumet Sales and Service Branch, Chicago-Midway Sales and Service Branch, 1973-1975; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 2, Folder 1)
        1/24/73 - 1/23/75.
      - Item 5: Clark Equipment Company, Brown Trailer Division, 1973-1976; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 2, Folder 1)
        10/25/73 - 10/24/76.
    - Clark Equipment Company, Tyler Refrigeration Division, Niles, Michigan and AIW, Local 816, 1972-1979; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 2, Folder 2)
      - Item 1: Clark Equipment Company, Tyler Refrigeration Division, Niles, Michigan and AIW, Local 816, 1972-1975; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 2, Folder 2)
        4/15/72 - 4/15/75.
      - Item 2: Clark Equipment Company, Tyler Refrigeration Division, Niles, Michigan and AIW, Local 816, 1975-1979; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 2, Folder 2)
        10/13/75 - 4/15/79.
    - Clark Equipment Company, Industrial Truck Division, Ross Carrier, Benton Harbor, Michigan and AIW, Local 835, 1955-1958; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 2, Folder 3)
      12/26/55 - 11/1/58.
    - Clark Equipment Company, Industrial Truck Division, Battle Creek, Michigan and AIW, Local 939, 1955-1983; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 2, Folder 4)
      - Item 1: Clark Equipment Company, Industrial Truck Division, Battle Creek, Michigan and AIW, Local 939, 1955-1958; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 2, Folder 4)
      - Item 2: Clark Equipment Company, Supplemental Unemployment Benefit Plan and Pension Plan, 1962; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 2, Folder 4)
      - Item 3: Clark Equipment Company, Industrial Truck Division, Battle Creek, Michigan and AIW, Local 939, 1977-1980; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 2, Folder 4)
        5/1/77 - 4/30/80.
      - Item 4: Clark Equipment Company, Industrial Truck Division, Battle Creek, Michigan and AIW, Local 939, 1980-1983; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 2, Folder 4)
        5/1/80 - 4/30/83.
    - Clark Equipment Company, Brown Trailer Division, Michigan City, Indiana and UAW, Local 1265, 1974-1977; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 2, Folder 5)
      4/27/74 - 4/22/77.
    - Clark Equipment Company, Construction Machinery Division, Benton Harbor, Michigan and UAW, Local 1290, 1956-1980; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 2, Folder 6)
      - Item 1: Clark Equipment Company, Construction Machinery Division, Benton Harbor, Michigan and UAW, Local 1290, 1956-1959; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 2, Folder 6)
        4/2/56 - 3/30/59.
      - Item 2: Clark Equipment Company, Construction Machinery Division, Benton Harbor, Michigan and UAW, Local 1290, 1956-1959; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 2, Folder 6)
        4/2/56 - 3/30/59. Copy 2.
      - Item 3: Clark Equipment Company, Construction Machinery Division, Benton Harbor, Michigan and UAW, Local 1290, 1977-1980; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 2, Folder 6)
        5/16/77 - 6/15/80.
    - Clark Equipment Company, Industrial Truck Division, Cleveland Sales & Service Branch and IAM, Local 1363, District 54, 1962-1964; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 2, Folder 7)
      4/2/62 - 4/2/64.
    - Clark Equipment Company and IAM, Lodge 1546 (East Bay Automotive Machinists) & Auto Painters Local No. 1176, B.P.D. & P. of America, 1962-1976; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 2, Folder 8)
      - Item 1: Clark Equipment Company, Brown Trailer Division, Oakland Sales & Service Branch, Oakland, California and IAM, Lodge 1546 (East Bay Automotive Machinists) & Auto Painters Local No. 1176, B.P.D. & P. of America, 1962-1965; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 2, Folder 8)
        9/1/62 - 8/31/65.
      - Item 2: Clark Equipment Company, Industrial Truck Division, Sales & Service Branch, Oakland California vs IAM, East Bay Automotive Machinists, Lodge 1546, 1973-1976; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 2, Folder 8)
        8/1/73 - 7/31/76.
    - Clark Equipment Company, Brown Trailer Division, Linden Sales and Service Branch, Linden, New Jersey vs IAM, Lodge 1697, District 47, 1962-1964; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 2, Folder 9)
      3/28/62 - 3/27/64.
    - Clark Equipment Company, Brown Trailer Division, Spokane, Washington and USA, Local 3785, 1962-1964; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 2, Folder 10)
      6/1/62 - 5/31/64.
    - Clausing, Inc. and USA, Local 6783., 1974-1980; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 2, Folder 11)
      - Item 1: Clausing, Inc. and USA, Local 6783., 1974-1977; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 2, Folder 11)
        11/25/74 - 11/25/77.
      - Item 2: Clausing, Inc. and USA, Local 6783., 1978-1980; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 2, Folder 11)
        2/20/78 - 2/20/80.
    - Continental Can Company, Inc. and USA. Master Agreement., 1955-1957; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 2, Folder 12)
      10/1/55 - 9/30/57.
    - Copeland Corporation and International Union of Electronic, Electrical, Technical, Salaried and Machine Workers (IUE), Local 769 & Local 725., Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Cuno Engineering Corporation, Meriden, Connecticut and UAW, Local 753, 1955-1957; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 2, Folder 14)
      9/26/55 - 9/26/57.
    - Dalton Foundries, Inc., Warsaw, Indiana and USA, Local 6805, 1973-1993; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 2, Folder 15)
      - Item 1: Dalton Foundries, Inc., Warsaw, Indiana and USA, Local 6805, 1973-1976; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 2, Folder 15)
        1/14/73 - 1/14/76.
      - Item 2: Dalton Foundries, Inc., Warsaw, Indiana and USA, Local 6805, 1973-1976; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 2, Folder 15)
        1/14/73 - 1/14/76. Copy 2.
      - Item 3: Dalton Foundries, Inc., Warsaw, Indiana and USA, Local 6805, 1976-1979; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 2, Folder 15)
        1/26/76 - 1/26/79.
      - Item 4: Dalton Foundries, Inc., Warsaw, Indiana and USA, Local 6805, 1981-1985; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 2, Folder 15)
        12/18/81 - 3/30/85.
      - Item 5: Dalton Foundries, Inc., Warsaw, Indiana and USA, Local 6805, 1981-1985; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 2, Folder 15)
        12/18/81 - 3/30/85. Copy 2.
      - Item 6: Dalton Foundries, Inc., Warsaw, Indiana and USA, Local 6805, 1985-1988; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 2, Folder 15)
        3/30/85 - 3/27/88.
      - Item 7: Dalton Foundries, Inc., Warsaw, Indiana and USA, Local 6805, 1985-1988; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 2, Folder 15)
        3/30/85 - 3/27/88. Copy 2.
      - Item 8: Dalton Foundries, Inc., Warsaw, Indiana and USA, Local 6805, 1988-1993; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 2, Folder 15)
        1/1/88 - 3/27/93.
      - Item 9: Dalton Foundries, Inc., Warsaw, Indiana and USA, Local 6805, 1988-1993; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 2, Folder 15)
        1/1/88 - 3/27/93. Copy 2.
    - Dana Corporation, 1971-1989; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 2, Folder 16)
      - Item 1: Dana Corporation, Churubusco Distribution Center, Oil Seal Plant, Churubusco and IAM, Local 2034, District Lodge 113, 1975-1978; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 2, Folder 16)
        10/18/75 - 10/21/78.
      - Item 2: Dana Corporation, Spicer Axle Division, Fort Wayne Plant and AIW, Local 903, 1971-1974; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 2, Folder 16)
        1/15/71 - 1/19/74.
      - Item 3: Dana Corporation, Spicer Axle Division, Fort Wayne Plant and AIW, Local 903, 1974-1977; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 2, Folder 16)
        1/20/74 - 1/22/77.
      - Item 4: Dana Corporation vs UAW, Local 370, New Castle Production and Maintenance Unit. Master Agreement and Local Supplement, 1986-1989; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 2, Folder 16)
        12/8/86 - 12/4/89.
    - Dayton Division of Dayton-Walther Corp. and USA, Local 4760, 1973-1976; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 2, Folder 17)
      - Item 1: Dayton Division of Dayton-Walther Corp., Foundry Division and USA, Local 4760, 1973-1976; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 2, Folder 17)
        7/8/73 - 7/31/76.
      - Item 2: Dayton Division of Dayton-Walther Corp., Machine Division and USA, Local 4760, 1973-1976; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 2, Folder 17)
      - Item 3: Dayton Division of Dayton-Walther Corp. and USA, Local Union 5028 & 4760. Pension Agreement, 1973-1976; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - DePuy and AIW, Local 809, 1986-1989; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 2, Folder 18)
      7/1/86 - 6/30/89.
    - Detroit Edison Company and Utility Workers Union of America (UWU), Local 223, 1949-1950; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 2, Folder 19)
      8/31/49 - 8/1/50
    - Diversitech General, a GenCorp Company and URW, Local 466, 1986-1989; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 2, Folder 20)
      8/1/86 - 8/1/89
    - Fisher Body Division, General Motors Corporation & Marion Plant and UAW, Local 977, 1979; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 2, Folder 21)
      10/1/1979
    - FMC Corporation, Bearing and Chain Division, Indianapolis and USA, Local 1150., 1979-1982; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 2, Folder 22)
      - Item 1: FMC Corporation, Bearing and Chain Division, Indianapolis and USA, Local 1150., 1979-1982; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 2, Folder 22)
        10/1/79 - 9/30/82.
      - Item 2: FMC Corporation, Bearing and Chain Division, Indianapolis and USA, Local 1150 Insurance Agreement and Dental Expense Benefit Plan., 1979- 1982; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 2, Folder 22)
      - Item 3: FMC Corporation, Bearing and Chain Division, Indianapolis and USA, Local 1150 Supplemental Agreements, 1979-1982; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Foote Bros. Gear and Machine Corporation and UE, Local 1114., 1946-1948; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 2, Folder 23)
      4/1/46 - 4/31/48.
    - Fort Wayne Works of International Harvester Company and Fort Wayne Die Sinkers' Lodge No. 80 of the International Die Sinkers' Conference., 1951-1955; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 2, Folder 24)
      1/9/51 - 6/30/55
    - Frost Gear and Forge Division of Clark Equipment Co. and UAW, Local 623, 1939-1940; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 2, Folder 25)
      8/18/39 - 8/18/40.
      - Item 1: Frost Gear and Forge Division of Clark Equipment Co. and UAW, Local 623, 1939-1940; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 2, Folder 25)
      - Item 2: Frost Gear and Forge Division of Clark Equipment Co. and UAW, Local 623, 1939-1940; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 2, Folder 25)
        8/18/39 - 8/18/40. Copy 2.
    - Fruehauf Corp. (Fruehauf Div., Fort Wayne Plant), and AIW, Local 776., 1963-1984; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 2, Folder 26)
      - Item 1: Fruehauf Corp. (Fruehauf Div., Fort Wayne Plant), and AIW, Local 776., 1963-1966; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 2, Folder 26)
        6/20/63 - 6/20/66.
      - Item 2: Fruehauf Corp. (Fruehauf Div., Fort Wayne Plant), and AIW, Local 776., 1972-1975; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 2, Folder 26)
        8/31/72 - 6/25/75.
      - Item 3: Fruehauf Corp. (Fruehauf Div., Fort Wayne Plant), and AIW, Local 776., 1975-1978; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 2, Folder 26)
        9/1/75 - 6/25/78.
      - Item 4: Fruehauf Corp. (Fruehauf Div., Fort Wayne Plant), and AIW, Local 776., 1978-1981; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 2, Folder 26)
        6/26/78 - 6/25/81.
      - Item 5: Fruehauf Corp. (Fruehauf Div., Fort Wayne Plant), and AIW, Local 776., 1981-1984; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 2, Folder 26)
        6/26/81 - 6/22/84.
    - Fuller Manufacturing Company, Transmission Division and UAW, Local 822., 1944-1949; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 2, Folder 27)
      1/22/44 - 6/30/49.
    - Gar Wood Industries, Inc., Findlay Division, Findlay Plant, Findlay, Ohio and IAM, Lodge 1194., 1953-1954; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 2, Folder 28)
      6/1/53 - 6/1/54.
    - General Motors Corporation and UAW-CIO., 1950-1955; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 2, Folder 29)
      - Item 1: General Motors Corporation and UAW-CIO., 1950-1955; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 2, Folder 29)
        5/29/50 - 5/29/55.
      - Item 2: General Motors Corporation and UAW-CIO Supplemental Agreements covering Pension Plan and Insurance Plan., 1950-1955; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - General Tire & Rubber Company, Akron, Ohio, Tire & Tube Plant and URW, Local 9., 1973-1982; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 2, Folder 30)
      - Item 1: General Tire & Rubber Company, Akron, Ohio, Tire & Tube Plant and URW, Local 9., 1973-1976; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 2, Folder 30)
        7/7/73 - 5/15/76.
      - Item 2: General Tire & Rubber Company, Industrial Products Division, Wabash, Indiana and URW, Local 626, 1976-1979; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 2, Folder 30)
        7/26/76 - 6/29/79.
      - Item 3: General Tire & Rubber Company, Industrial Products Division, Wabash, Indiana and URW, Local 626, 1979-1982; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 2, Folder 30)
        6/29/79 - 6/29/82.
    - Golden Foundry, Inc. and IMAW, Local 86., 1974-1977; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 2, Folder 31)
      7/14/74 - 7/13/77.
    - Goodyear Tire and Rubber Company of Michigan and URW, Jackson Plant, Local 185., 1947-1982; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 2, Folder 32)
      - Item 1: Goodyear Tire and Rubber Company of Michigan and URW, Jackson Plant, Local 185., 1947-1948; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 2, Folder 32)
        6/9/47 - 6/1/48.
      - Item 2: Goodyear Tire and Rubber Company of Michigan and URW, Jackson Plant, Local 185., 1979-1982; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 2, Folder 32)
        9/6/79 -4/20/82.
    - Grabler Mfg. Co., Cleveland, Ohio and USA, Local 1309, 1951-1952; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 2, Folder 33)
      5/1/51 - 4/30/52.
    - Hayes-Albion Corporation, Jackson Division and UAW, Local 327., 1977-1980; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 2, Folder 34)
      3/1/77 - 2/28/80.
    - Hillsdale Steel Products, Division of Dana Corporation, Hillsdale, Michigan and UAW, Local 663, 1948-1950; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 2, Folder 35)
      - Item 1: Hillsdale Steel Products, Division of Dana Corporation, Hillsdale, Michigan and UAW, Local 663, 1948-1950; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 2, Folder 35)
        6/30/48 - 6/30/50.
      - Item 2: Hillsdale Steel Products, Division of Dana Corporation, Hillsdale, Michigan and UAW, Local 663, 1948-1950; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 2, Folder 35)
        6/30/48 - 6/30/50. Copy 2.
    - Houdaille-Hershey Corporation and UAW, Local 932, 332, 850, 673, 992., 1947-1949; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 2, Folder 36)
      6/20/47 - 6/11/49.
    - International Harvester Company, 1946-1964; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 3, Folder 1)
      - Item 1: International Harvester Company, Fort Wayne Works and DSC, Local 80., 1946-1947; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 3, Folder 1)
        9/9/46 - 9/9/47.
      - Item 2: International Harvester Company and UAW, Locals 6, 57, 76, 98, 111, 226, 402, 792, 817, 988, 1101, 1145, 1301, 1304, 1306, 1307, 1308, 1309, 1310, 1336, 1357, 305, 658, 894, 1012, 1274, 1302, 1303, 1333, 1356, 1361, 1382. Supplemental Agreements and Lett, 1959; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 3, Folder 1)
        1/16/1959.
      - Item 3: International Harvester Company and American Federation of Technical Engineers, Local 137, 1950-1955; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 3, Folder 1)
        12/12/50 - 12/12/55.
      - Item 4: International Harvester Company and American Federation of Technical Engineers, Local 137, 1962-1964; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 3, Folder 1)
        6/6/62 - 10/1/64.
    - International Harvester Company, 1964-1967; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 3, Folder 2)
      - Item 1: International Harvester Company and UAW, Locals 305, 658, 894, 1333, 1356, 1361, 1382. Clerical and Technical Main Labor Contract., 1964-1967; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 3, Folder 2)
        10/7/64 - 10/1/67.
      - Item 2: International Harvester Company and UAW, Locals 6, 57, 76, 98, 152, 226, 402, 792, 817, 988, 1145, 1301, 1304, 1306, 1307, 1309, 1310, 1336, 1357. Production and Maintenance Main Labor Contract, 1964-1967; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 3, Folder 2)
      - Item 3: International Harvester Company Summary of Health-Security Program, Non-Contributory Retirement Plan, Supplemental Unemployment Benefit Plan, 1964; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 3, Folder 2)
        10/7/64.
      - Item 4: International Harvester Company Summary of Health-Security Program, Non-Contributory Retirement Plan, Supplemental Unemployment Benefit Plan, 1964- 1967; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 3, Folder 2)
      - Item 5: International Harvester Company Supplemental Documents to the 1964 Master Contracts covering Hourly and Salaried Employes, Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 3, Folder 2)
        10/7/1964.
      - Item 6: International Harvester Company and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, Local 1608, 1964-1967; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 3, Folder 2)
        10/23/64 - 10/1/67.
    - International Harvester Company, 1968-1970; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 3, Folder 2A)
      - Item 1: International Harvester Company and UAW, Locals 305, 658, 894, 1333, 1356, 1361, 1382. Clerical and Technical Main Labor Contract, 1968-1970; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 3, Folder 2A)
        2/6/68 - 10/1/70.
      - Item 2: International Harvester Company and UAW, Locals 305, 658, 894, 1333, 1356, 1361, 1382. Clerical and Technical Main Labor Contract, 1968-1970; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 3, Folder 2A)
        2/6/68 - 10/1/70. Copy 2.
      - Item 3: International Harvester Company and UAW, Locals 6, 57, 76, 98, 119, 152, 226, 305, 402, 472, 505, 658, 688, 710, 763, 792, 792A, 817, 894, 969, 988, 1004, 1077, 1089, 1089A, 1115, 1145, 1152, 1301, 1304, 1306, 1307, 1309, 1310, 1333A, 1333B, 1336, 1356, 1, 1968-1970; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 3, Folder 2A)
        Health-Security Program, Non-Contributory Retirement Plan, Supplemental Unemployment Benefit Plan. 2/6/68 - 10/1/70.
    - International Harvester Company, 1971-1973; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 3, Folder 3)
      - Item 1: International Harvester Company and UAW, Locals 6, 57, 76, 98, 152, 226, 402, 792, 817, 988, 1077, 1145, 1301, 1304, 1306, 1307, 1309, 1310, 1336, 1357, 1486, 1643. Production and Maintenance Mail Labor Contract, 1971-1973; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 3, Folder 3)
        1/29/71 - 10/1/73.
      - Item 2: International Harvester Company and UAW, Locals 305, 658, 792A, 894, 1333A, 1333B, 1356, 1361, 1382 and 1543. Clerical and Technical Mail Labor Contract, 1971-1973; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 3, Folder 3)
      - Item 3: International Harvester Company and Society of Engineering Employees, Inc., Motor Truck Engineering Department, Office and Technical Employes, 1971- 1973; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 3, Folder 3)
        3/15/71 - 10/1/73.
      - Item 4: International Harvester Company Professional Employes., 1971-1973; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 3, Folder 3)
      - Item 5: International Harvester Company and American Federation of Technical Engineers, AFL-CIO, Local 137., 1971-1973; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 3, Folder 3)
        3/9/71 - 10/1/73.
      - Item 6: International Harvester Company and IBEW, Local 1608., 1971-1973; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 3, Folder 3)
        4/13/71 - 01/1/73.
    - International Harvester Company and UAW, Locals 305, 658, 894, 1077A, 1333A, 1333B, 1356, 1361. Clerical and Technical Main Labor Contract., 1973- 1979; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 3, Folder 4)
      - Item 1: International Harvester Company and UAW, Locals 305, 658, 894, 1077A, 1333A, 1333B, 1356, 1361. Clerical and Technical Main Labor Contract., 1973- 1976; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 3, Folder 4)
        11/8/73 - 10/1/76.
      - Item 2: International Harvester Company and UAW, Locals 305, 658, 894, 1077A, 1333A, 1333B, 1356, 1361. Clerical and Technical Main Labor Contract., 1973- 1976; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 3, Folder 4)
      - Item 3: International Harvester Company and UAW, Locals 305, 658, 894, 1077A, 1333A, 1333B, 1356, 1361. Clerical and Technical Main Labor Contract., 1976- 1979; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 3, Folder 4)
        10/30/76 - 10/1/79.
      - Item 4: International Harvester Company and UAW, Locals 6, 57, 76, 98, 152, 226, 402, 817, 988, 1077, 1145, 1304, 1306, 1307, 1309, 1310, 1336, 1357, 1643. Production and Maintenance Main Labor Contract, 1973-1976; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 3, Folder 4)
      - Item 5: International Harvester Company and IBEW, Local 1608, 1974-1976; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 3, Folder 4)
        1/24/74 - 10/1/76.
    - International Telephone and Telegraph Corporation, Aerospace/Optical Division and UE, Local 999, 1974-1977; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 3, Folder 5)
      8/29/74-8/28/77.
    - Jackson Crankshaft Division of Muskegon Motor Specialties Company and UAW, Local 953, 1947-1978; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 3, Folder 6)
      - Item 1: Jackson Crankshaft Division of Muskegon Motor Specialties Company and UAW, Local 953, 1947-1949; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 3, Folder 6)
        10/6/47 - 6/11/49.
      - Item 2: Jackson Crankshaft Company and UAW, Local 953, 1975-1978; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 3, Folder 6)
        6/22/75 - 9/1/78.
      - Item 3: Jackson Crankshaft Company and UAW, Local 953, 1978-1981; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 3, Folder 6)
        6/26/78 - 9/1/81.
      - Item 4: Jackson Crankshaft Company and UAW, Local 953 Supplemental Agreement., 1975-1981; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 3, Folder 6)
        6/22/75 - 8/31/81.
      - Item 5: Jackson Crankshaft Company and UAW, Local 953 Supplemental Agreement., 1975-1981; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Kelsey-Hayes Wheel Company and UAW, Local 670, 1947-1951; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 3, Folder 7)